http://www.pro-artdentallab.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyOur Commitment to YouPro-Art is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. Any personal information provided by site users will be protected to the extent possible and will not be released to third parties.
Privacy OfficerPlease direct any questions or complaints regarding privacy issues to Mr. George Polak at 416-469-4121 ext. 249 or e-mail him at  george@pro-artdentallab.com .
Collection of InformationPro-Art collects personal information solely to assist us in providing potential clients with more information concerning our products and services. Personal information is expressly provided by potential clients through our “Contact Us” user interface.
Use of InformationAll registration information is stored on a secure server unavailable to anyone outside of Pro-Art. None of the registration information is ever provided to third-party organizations. The information is regarded and treated by Pro-Art as confidential business information for its internal use only.
CookiesCookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer browsing the website and are used for record keeping purposes at many websites. Cookies perform various functions, such as saving your passwords and saving your personal preferences with respect to a particular website (personalized portals).
Your browser is probably set to accept Cookies. However, if you prefer not to receive Cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse them. If you choose to have your browser refuse Cookies, it's possible that some areas of our site that may use Cookies will not function properly when you attempt view them. We use Cookies only to keep a record of visitors to our website. Pro-Art does not share or disclose this information to third parties.
ModificationsPro-Art encourages users of our website to review the Privacy Policy Statement periodically. Pro-Art reserves the right to revise these terms without notice. Unless otherwise provided, the revised terms will take effect at the time of posting on the site.
Thank you for subscribing
Thank you for subscribing!
Thank you for contacting us
Your message has been received. We will do our best to contact you as soon as possible.
Thank you for contacting us
Your message has been received. We will do our best to contact you as soon as possible.
Thank you for contacting us
Your message has been received. We will do our best to contact you as soon as possible.
